Finally awake?
Yuji-niisan...
You shouldn't move if you don't have to.
That wound I closed for you might open back up.
Why did you go out of
your way to let me live?
What do you want?
Money? A transfer back to the main office?
I have money.
And besides, getting rid of you won't
get me back to the head office.
I'm finished.
If you know that, why would you do a thing like this?
You're asking me why?
You're asking me why!?
Both you and Kazuhisa!
Are profits all you can think about!?
Can't you find a purpose in anything but your careers!?
As I kill you, I'll make sure you suffer more than I ever did.
I see...
So this is about revenge.
What's so funny!?
hatenai sora
Endless skies
kinou to wa chigau massara na kimochi wa
You've got this brand new feeling, one different than yesterday's
honki no kotoba wo koete motto riaru ni
It's more real than any words can describe
"kono mama ja iya da" sou itte nakidashita
You cry to yourself, "I don't want things to go on like this"
ano hi no kimi no chikai sukoshi kurai mie wo hattatte ii
But you should at least hold yourself to the vows you made
kawaranai kako shinjita mirai subete ukeireru keredo
You may be done with your past and believing in your future,
hitorikiri ja totemo kakaekirenai
but you can't face all of it alone
hakanai sora setsunai ketsui
Ephemeral skies. Hold on to your wistful determination,
mujuun datte kamawanai
as contradictory as it may be
nakama to miru yume yo, kobaruto ni somare
I'll reach my dreams together with my friends as we dye everything in cobalt
hirumu mamonaku moyashi zukuse
Don't hold back. Set everything ablaze:
namida mo egao mo yuu'utsu saemo
our tears, our smiles, and even our sorrows
ima hiraketa sekai fumidasu inochi
Take heart as the world opens up
unmei nante kaerareru
We can change our destiny
hashiridashita kaze yo, kobaruto ni somare
These winds that are building will dye everything in cobalt
kagirinaku riaru ni
and make them more real than ever before
Where did you get this?
Just as I thought. You've covered it up, haven't you?
An unsightly scandal like this... I can't let it go public.
What's the current situation?
Is Nagisa-sama alive?
I haven't heard anything yet.
I'm having all of the Kirishina Warehouse facilities searched.
Do you really intend to save him?
This is a Kiryu family issue.
I only have so many pawns I can put on this.
I never dreamed Yuji would stoop to such idiocy.
A man like you...
Even if you can read every intention of your most formidable enemies and reliable allies,
I don't think you could begin to imagine how the less fortunate think.
Are you implying that this is my fault?
It's pointless to argue over whose fault it is.
We don't have that kind of time.
And besides...
Nagisa-sama has made that same mistake.
Episode 12:
Hope, Ambition,
and Dispair
It's been almost six hours since Nagisa-sama was abducted.
I did everything I possibly could,
but the only thing I found out was that neither the police nor the company can be trusted.
So all I can do now is rely on you.
It's true that Nagisa-sama might have deserted you.
And perhaps he failed to save A-TEC.
But...
First, we've got to retrace Kiryu's steps up till the moment he was taken.
Yeah, the perp might've been following him.
If we can figure out how he knew about that hotel, it might tell us something.
Sakugo, do you remember Nagisa's ID and password you hacked from our graduation trip?
He's probably already changed them.
You can just hack them back, can't you?
Of course I can!
Um... Are you sure about this?
About what?
Well, Nagisa-sama assumed you would all resent him after what he did.
Of course we do!
That's why we're gonna rescue him and make him our slave.
Can't wait to try the sweets the director brings back!
I'm sure they'll be totally delicious!
Um, you guys...
Can't we find a better reason?
Hey, you need to help out too, Hanako-chan!
Weren't you the last person to see the chief?
Didn't I tell you to stop calling me that?
You snot-nosed brat!
Don't worry.
We'll find him, you hear?
Okay.
Wait...
This is the car that was parked in front of the hotel the day before!
And it's near where the black van was abandoned!
Bingo, that's it.
Can you track it?
Leave it to me!
This is near Yunoumi.
I'm heading over.
Tell me if you find anything new!
What's this?
Nagisa... you...
You...
I'm coming, too.
I can drive faster.
I heard from Sera-sensei...
With that condition of yours, I don't think you should...
It's all right! It's not a problem at all!
You'd only get in the way like this.
If we're going to save Nagisa-sama,
we need to go with our best possible chance.
We can't sit around and wait for you to heal!
Don't worry.
One day, we're going to need you for sure.
So just be patient.
Yunoumi Town
It's no good. I can't narrow it down any more.
We picked up over 300 cars.
How many days would it take for us to track them all down?
Find them all, no matter how long it takes!
G-Gotcha.
You guys, I have something important to tell you.
Stop what you're doing and listen to me.
Thank you for working so late tonight.
But...
For now, we're going home.
Nii-san?
What are you talking about?
Starting tomorrow... no, this morning,
we're going to start repairs on the X-3.
So get as much rest as you can.
What are you talking about, Sera Kaito!?
Are you telling us to abandon him?!
Sensei... why?
It's because we're not abandoning him that we are doing what we can do.
DDY Tasty
Restructur Plan (Draft)
Restructuring Plan (Draft)
(   )
A-TEC reorganization plan, rough draft.
"A-TEC, please give your approval and support."
But this is...
What is that guy, a moron?
He's a moron, all right.
What did he get himself promoted for?
I mean, going out of his way to help out this failing rocket...
I told you, you shouldn't talk about the director like that.
(    )
Restructuring Plan (Draft)
To get this plan off the ground,
we've got to get cracking now!
(    )
Restructuring Plan (Draft)
No, we're two days behind already.
We can't afford any more delays.
B-But... If Nagisa-sama dies,
it'll do more harm than good!
Even if he does come back alive,
if A-TEC is gone, it will kill his ambition!
This plan isn't just the biggest rebellion of his life,
it's our chance to come back around!
So please...
I want you to save Nagisa's life.
What's this?
I looked into all of Nagisa's connections.
I'm gonna leave that battle to the specialists.
They're the right people for the job.
All right, no time to dilly-dally!
Yuna! Kaoruko!
I want you two to take on combat service support roles for Angelina-sensei.
But don't go into the field for any reason, okay?
Leave it to us, Sensei!
Let's go, Angelina-sensei!
To save Kiryu-san!
Tsubasa, you come with me.
We're redoing our presentation plans.
Roger!
And the rest of you will start the repairs on the X-3!
Mizuki...
You take command here.
N-Nii-san!
First, we need to come up with a schedule...
Okay!
Aki...
Mizuki-senpai, if you please.
We need your skills.
Restructuring Plan (Draft)
Yeah, since we need to make up for the two days we lost.
By the way, I think break time's over...
I thought we weren't going to mention it.
Let's go, A-TEC!
We'll rock this show no matter what!
Yeah!
Fourth Tokyo - Abandoned Underground
So you've finally regained consciousness, huh?
The real fun is about to start now.
Hey, Yuji-niisan...
How long have I been out?
What day is today?
Why would somebody who's about to die need to know that?
There isn't much time before A-TEC's in-house presentation.
I did leave a trail for them to follow,
but you know how slow they can be.
I wonder if they were able to see what my intent was.
And there's one matter that my plan alone can't resolve.
Were they able to find a substitute pilot?
Hey, Nii-san.
If you hear anything...
Presentation, my ass!
A-TEC, my ass!
Why don't you worry about yourself!?
You're barely alive,
but you're still happy at the mention of your job!
Well, I am a businessman.
I might as well just gut you right now so you won't have the pleasure.
Is that right?
I just wish I could live to see what happens to them.
Fine.
To grant my precious kid brother's wish, I'll move my plans back a little.
I'll let you live to witness the complete destruction of A-TEC!
Fourth Tokyo - West District No. 12 Wall
Cold Wood Corporation
Limited Company
Is that right? You were referred by Kiryu-san?
Cold Wood Corporation
Limited Company
Welcome! Glad to have you!
U-Um... are you sure this is the place?
And here I was sure it was a private eye's office, or a security firm.
Kiryu-san has done a lot for me.
When I launched my firm in Kirishina,
he became my guarantor, and even gave me leads.
I really owe him one.
Well, Kiryu has been taken by unknown abductors.
Oh, no! How could that have happened!?
Kiryu-san is a good guy, but he has lots of enemies.
I'll at least pray for his safety.
Would you mind dropping that annoying fake act already?
You haven't shown the slightest chink in your armor yet.
Who on earth are you?
Are you that Hattori Hanako that Nagisa's always talking about?
My name is Angelina.
Oh, so it's not you?
Then I have nothing to say to you.
I must ask you to leave.
Oh, come on!
Quit complicating things!
That's right, this is Hattori Hanako, who calls herself Angelina.
You heard that.
What's the current situation?
We haven't been able to locate Kiryu-san yet, either.
It looks like our GPS tracker's been found and destroyed.
I see.
At the moment, we're canvassing workers in each region.
I'll contact you once I hear anything new.
Can we really afford to be taking it so slow?
It'll take some time, but this is the most reliable method by far.
We've been tracing their movements till now,
but the enemy is very keen.
If we make too much of a splash and get made,
they'll run off in an instant.
That's right.
Once we find clear-cut evidence, that'll be our chance to attack.
Um... Wasn't this a construction company?
By day, we're a building contractor's office.
In other words, we have our share of hooligans.
They'll come in handy during the rescue mission.
The fuselage's finally here, huh?
Now we can start replacing parts.
Maybe we'll somehow squeak in under the wire?
Well, let's say we do make it in time...
are we really gonna launch this?
True, if this were to take flight, the impact would be mind-blowing.
Still, we've got to make it work.
For this presentation, we can't just focus on results,
but on impact as well.
We've got to show them how incredible our new SWNPR engine is!
Well, the bar's been set pretty high.
In-house Presentation
Attendance Confirmed
CEO Kiryu
VP Yanai
Thank you for your patronage.
I'm Hanaoka of the Advanced Technological Development Department.
I'm calling about the presentation we asked you to attend yesterday...
Yes... Yes...
Is that right?
Audit Yamashita
MD Aoki
Sr. MD Sawazaki
Audit Yamashita
Thank you very much!
MD Aoki
Audit Yamashita
Sr. MD Sawazaki
MD Aoki
Then we'll be seeing you on the day of the presentation!
Field Commander
Sera Mizuki
Presentation
Leader
Sera Kaito
Presentation
Assistant
Hanaoka Tsubasa
Test Pilot
Material Technician
Ryouke Makoto
Combustion Testing
Yamaki Subaru
Communications
Takanashi Kaoruko
Accountant
Nounen Yuna
Supervisor
Maioka Sakugo
Kaminagaya Aki
Engine Maintenance
Aircraft Design
Kitahara Kojiro
Organization Chart
For Day Of Presentation
【                       】
Main Office
Large Conf. Room
Eighth Manufacturing Plant
As for how to participate,
I'll send you that information by the end of the day.
Test Pilot
Day of the Presentation
February 1
And now it's time to say goodbye.
This will be your coffin, Nagisa.
Is this... the X-2's?
That's right!
The one nobody can catch. A-TEC's vaunted engine, the fastest in the known universe!
Now that's a glitzy burial in outer space, huh?
How in the world did you...
I told you that I had money.
I borrowed one that was mothballed and abandoned at another section.
Well, since we did just slap it onto an LGV,
I can't guarantee its durability!
You're going to vanish in the dust along with this A-TEC engine.
Not only that, but you'll be arriving at its destination, Cold Wood, in seven hours!
The same time the presentation starts!
Aren't you happy?
You'll be blown to bits along with your beloved A-TEC!
That's if you get there safely, though.
Yuji-niisan?
What is it? Is life suddenly precious to you?
I'm sorry.
Thanks to my trivial revenge,
I've made you unhappy, too.
No way am I gonna let you show me any sympathy!
This was my choice! My decision!
I did it all on my own!
It's almost time. Director...
Shinamiya Nagisa is finally going to vanish, huh?
You're okay with this, aren't you, Nagisa-sama?
What the hell!?
Dammit!
Did it come to save him!?
Hey! Do something about this!
I'm going to let Administration deal with you.
Hurry, Hanako!
This is going to take time!
Go to the control room and abort the launch!
I was going to do that anyway!
And don't call me by my real name!
Hanako!
Ibra-san! What's the situation?
Is Angelina-sensei... Is Kiryu all right?
The operation... failed.
minami kaze ga toorisugite yuku
The southern winds blowing through
sazanami ni awasete yureru kokoro
set my heart in motion like rippling waves
mayoi nante, hitotsumonaitte omoikomasete
Make me believe that I shouldn't be worried
asu, iemasuyouni
"Tomorrow. I'll say it then,"
nandomo kurikaeshi
is what I told myself over and over
omoikaeshi aruita
as I wandered aimlessly about
hanarebanare demo ii
I don't care if we're separated,
onnaji yume dewarai atte itai
I just want to laugh with you, sharing the same dream
demo ne honne wa ienai
I can't tell you my true feelings
mada ienaiyo
At least, not yet
tsuyogari ga yowane datte
I'm sure that you still don't know
kitto kimi wa mada wakaranai hazu
that pretending to be strong is my cry for help
aitai samishii
I want to see you, I'm lonely
kono mama tomodachi ja iyadayo
I don't want us to just be friends forever
That's what I heard from Kaoruko.
Did you say Cold Wood?
No way...
But we somehow managed to complete it!
So what are we gonna do, Kaitocchi?
Change of plans.
The mission to rescue Kiryu Nagisa
and A-TEC's in-house presentation... will be run simultaneously!