Shinamiya Nagisa is...
me?
We're going to start repairs on the X-3.
Are you telling us to abandon him!?
The mission to rescue Kiryu Nagisa
and A-TEC's in-house presentation... will be run simultaneously!
February 1
4 Hours Before
the Presentation
Advanced Technological
Development Department Building
Basement B10
Launching Zone
Where are you going, Iris?
Mizuki...
February 1
Start of Presentation
Did you say Cold Wood?
Yes. Yuji-sama just disclosed that to his lawyer.
Years of Achievements
Kirishina Corporation A-TEC
Does that mean he can be saved?
Unfortunately,
he's traveling at such a high speed that we can't track him, let alone rescue him.
From what I've been told, he's on course to collide with Cold Wood any minute now.
I see.
What do you want us to do?
That's an uninhabited satellite now.
After the collision, I want you to retrieve all of the wreckage.
Make sure you don't leave any traces.
Final Episode
The Greatest Presentation in History
All right, then...
The CEO is here, so I'd like to begin.
Right now,
the Advanced Technological Development Department, Educational Development Class,
also known as A-TEC,
will present—
Hold on a second, Chief Sera.
Or rather, Deputy Chief.
What is it, Vice President Yanai?
Do you understand what kind of situation we're in right now?
I understand that A-TEC's current status is dire.
Therefore, I hope that after we present our results,
you'll reconsider disbanding us.
Your boss has gone missing, you know!
Who do you think you are, doing a presentation at a time like this?
Oh, what does it matter?
Let's hear about Kaito's engine!
You can bet it's gonna be cool!
Naturally, we're also helping to search for Director Kiryu.
However, if we were to miss this opportunity,
when could we expect you all to be in the same room again?
Can we really expect you
to create another opportunity for us to make our appeal to you before you dismantle A-TEC?
All right, feel free to proceed.
However,
right now, the impression you're giving us isn't good.
That's fine by us.
All right, then, allow me to begin.
Disobeying orders again?
Planning on flying solo?
You're going to go rescue Nagisa-kun, aren't you?
In the X-3?
Well...
This will be the most dangerous thing you've ever done.
You could even die this time.
This isn't anything like the rockets you've flown before, Iris.
You're going to have to chase after the X-2 in an unfamiliar machine.
Nobody knows how powerful it is except for us, the builders.
And the biggest issue of all is
you're too afraid to fly right now!
Something came back to you, right?
You were never afraid of accidents or injuries previously,
but now your body just freezes up, doesn't it?
The feeling of fear
has returned, right?
It's got nothing to do with you, Mizuki.
Of course it has something to do with me.
How could I have nothing to do with you!?
Why would you hide it?
Why won't you tell me anything?
Why are you suddenly so concerned about Nagisa-kun?
You're scared, your hands are trembling,
your knees look like they're ready to give out...
Why do you wan't to save him so bad?
At approximately 420,000 km per hour,
the X-3's max speed is 1.7 times the X-2's,
and its fuel efficiency has doubled.
This has all been made possible thanks to our newly-developed successor model
to the SWNPR engine, the KSX-5.
Please take note of the engine's cost.
We at A-TEC were able to build it while operating under a 70% budget cut.
At this cost, we can achieve what was never possible before:
bringing the SWNPR engine to the masses.
If that comes to pass,
not only will it generate new demand for our company's faltering aerospace business,
it will facilitate the development of new resource planets
and also allow us to further contribute to the expansion of the entire galaxy.
Bravo!
Just what you'd expect from the whiz-kid of the engineering world!
Quality, cost, lead-time.
In all aspects, it's a truly innovative engine that's ahead of its time by leaps and bounds!
Thank you very much!
Oh, hey, I wonder
what would happen if we put those in one of my combat workers?
Li-sensei, I told you there's no longer any need for—
I have to admit, that was a magnificent presentation.
Quite laudable.
But it's only theoretical, not practical.
At the end of the day,
this was merely a win by Sera Kaito's brain,
rather than A-TEC's achievement.
You're wrong about that!
We at A-TEC have already tested this engine and validated its performance!
Then why didn't you build a test engine and demo it today?
Isn't that proof that you haven't actually finished it?
CEO...
I suppose this means that the students' skills aren't on par with Sera Kaito's concepts.
There's no point in keeping A-TEC going after all, eh?
It looks like they found out about the accident from the other day.
Yeah.
All according to plan.
All right, I'd like to show you all the X-3 engine's demo flight now.
First, let us show you footage from the guidance buoy closest to Cold Wood.
Cold Wood?
But that's...
Mizuki...
I...
My...
My real name is...
All right, all right, time's up!
Hey! I told you I was going to talk to her alone!
Who said you could listen in!?
I'm sorry, we just couldn't help ourselves.
But we don't have time for that now.
If you don't leave right after we make a final check,
you won't be able to catch the X-2 before it crashes into Cold Wood!
Prepare for standby, please!
But Iris was just about to really open up to me.
Mizuki, what's going on?
Sorry.
It's really the other way around.
Other way around?
I didn't come here to stop you, Iris.
I came here to talk you into flying!
We never managed to find a pilot to replace you.
We just couldn't find anyone as good as you, Iris.
I know what condition you're in.
I know that you normally wouldn't be allowed to fly
without a medical advisor's approval.
Even so, I made up my mind to ask you to do this, Iris.
As the acting supervisor here, I'm asking you...
No, I'm ordering you...
Iris, fly it!
Go rescue Nagisa-kun!
Okay.
Iris...
But I'm doing this on my own.
You're not responsible in any way, Mizuki.
No.
You'll be following my orders.
I'll take responsibility for it all.
It's my job to save him.
You're wrong. You're going to rescue Nagisa-kun because I want you to.
When you don't even know who he really is?
What!? What's that supposed to mean!?
Since when do you talk down to me like that, Iris?
Save the arguments for after the mission, will you?
Mizuki-senpai, please get changed into your space suit, too.
All right.
You're boarding, too, Mizuki?
Of course!
You're going to need a crew member who knows both the machine and you, right?
But...
Anyhow, can you treat Nagisa-kun's injuries after you've rescued him?
Well...
That's why I'm coming with you.
Driving
Safety
Let's come back together, all three of us!
Okay.
All systems go!
Iris-senpai, Mizuki-senpai, here we go!
Copy that.
Is that the Shinamiya rocket!?
Yes.
We've loaded the latest X-3 engine into the machine
that Shinamiya Renichiro developed 70 years ago,
upon which the Kirishina Corporation was built!
That's an antique item stored in the Kirishina Memorial Building!
Due to various reasons, this was the only machine we could provide for today's presentation.
This is ludicrous!
What possible purpose could this stunt flight have!?
But it does have a purpose!
Please try to remember the reason why A-TEC was founded!
Why A-TEC was founded?
What Shinamiya Renichiro preached,
integration of new ideas with traditional technology,
the fusion of the X-3 and the Shinamiya rocket,
they represent his philosophy perfectly, wouldn't you say?
As if that old machine could withstand the thrust of a cutting-edge engine!
It would crumble in an instant, scattering across the galaxy.
It's taken off from Mars, and is about to reach Cold Wood as we speak!
A trip that would take even the X-2 seven hours has been slashed to four.
Moreoever, we haven't run into any complications yet,
despite how outdated the machine is.
But the fact that it can do this is no achievement of my own.
There are people who replaced all of the steering gear and avionics in a short time,
so that it could function in an older machine,
and made it a viable vehicle once again!
Those same people are working to ensure that the pilot will reach her destination safely,
supporting her to their utmost until she returns!
And right now,
there are people staking everything they have in order to rescue their beloved friend!
These people can make the impossible possible!
If I can continue working with them, we can achieve anything!
And that's why I want to continue laughing with them, crying with them,
and working with them forever.
Visual confirmation of the X-2.
Copy that.
Nagisa-kun!
Iris-senpai! Mizuki-senpai!
There's no room for error. You've only got one chance!
Copy that.
Iris!
Yay!
All right.
Bravo!
What was the rocket you just rescued?
That was just a demonstration
to show you the extent of X-3's capabilities.
Thank you, Iris.
That's our ace!
Mizuki...
Iris, you look after Nagisa-kun.
I'll be there as soon as I'm done checking the machine.
Hang in there... Hang in there!
No...
I can't take this...
Please, open your eyes!
Nagisa-sama...
Why did you have to come after me?
Didn't I tell you that I'd protect you?
Nagisa-sama...
From now on,
I'll be the one to protect you.
But now that you've rescued me... I've totally lost face, huh?
Nagisa-kun!
Iris!
I've just received word that Kiryu-san is safe!
This concludes A-TEC's end-of-term report.
I'd like to ask you all one more time.
Do you still wish to dismantle A-TEC?
The treasure of the rocket industry. No, the industrial industry...
Are you going to let it go without a fight?
A-TEC's disbanding was officially approved at our previous directors' meeting.
B-But CEO,
after we've seen such tremendous results...
Not only that, but we can foresee major cost reductions.
You could say that there's no longer any reason to dismantle it...
I can't overturn that decision now.
That's how corporations work.
As a businessman, you should know that yourself.
Are you really sure, CEO?
You're being a pest, Sera-kun!
Well, it's not like I was hoping you'd come to our rescue anyway.
Hey, Yuna! How's it going? What do the investors say?
Investors?
I see! We've already collected 60 billion?
All right! We've surpassed last year's annual budget then, huh?
Now we can really go to town on R&D!
No, we can't!
After everything we had to go through this term,
I won't let you waste our funds again!
What did you do?
Oh, hey, you know how our
accounting manager's such a nag.
What did you do, Sera Kaito!?
A-TEC's to be dismantled.
That was your decision, correct?
Resignation
Letter  of
Therefore, all of us at A-TEC will
resign and set up our own shop.
And it seems like we'll have no shortage of sponsors!
Actually, that demo footage you just saw wasn't just streamed in-house,
but to all the corporations and investors who've ever taken an interest in A-TEC.
It seems like plenty of people
are interested in and willing to help us develop our new company.
Was this your idea, Sera?
Resignation
Letter of
Nagisa
Kiryu
It was Nagisa's doing?
Listen up, Kiryu Kazuhisa...
Letter  of
Resignation
We refuse to acknowledge your way of doing things!
W-Why, you...
There are some things in life that you just can't buy with money.
Do you know what they are?
They're aspirations!
A-TEC doesn't seek money-making technologies!
Nor technologies for war!
But rather, technologies that will put smiles on our customers' faces!
We don't need the Nobel Prize in Physics!
Why? Because we're gonna win the Nobel Peace Prize!
Hey, hey...
I joined your company because you said I could get my hands on Kaito's engine!
Sera, you're forgetting something very important.
Even if your group leaves this company, the X-3 engine still belongs to Kirishina.
Is that true!?
Well, since the engine was built with the company's money and facilities...
In other words,
no matter how we intend to use it,
once you're gone, there's nothing that you can do about it.
Then can I install it into my combat workers!?
What!?
You don't know how to close a deal, do you, Sera Kaito?
Nagisa...
Hey, Kazuhisa-niisan...
You're right, the X-3 belongs to Kirishina.
As ex-employees, we have no right to manufacture or sell them.
You realized that, and you still insist on leaving Kirishina?
Don't be such a sore loser.
What do you mean?
What you really wanted wasn't a cutting-edge engine...
You were after the person named Sera Kaito,
who made it functional within six months, right?
Me?
You made the wrong choice.
If you really wanted Kaito,
you should've just taken possession of A-TEC itself from the start and
its bunch of morons and all.
Take the X-3 engine.
After all, we've got a team
that can turn a cutting-edge engine into an old-school one in six months.
The best team ever!
I'll give them 100 billion...
C-CEO!?
So come back, Nagisa!
Didn't Kaito tell you?
We don't acknowledge your way of doing things, Nii-san.
You're going to regret this.
Let's see who's going to regret things more.
All right!
Iris?
What was that for!?
This man is...
Hold on a second, both of you...
Get away from my little sister, Nagisa!
You've got the wrong idea! I was just...
And since when did you start two-timing!?
Yasuhisa Kiryu
It's not time for you to step up yet, Father.
Hey, there, Nagisa-kun!
You've got two beauties visiting you today!
Huh?
Hey, Kaito?
What do you think I should do?
How should I know? Think for yourself!
But if you ever make Mizuki cry...
Nagisa-sama!
Hattori-kun?
As you requested, I've scouted an executive for your new company!
A-TEC, Inc.
Launch Ceremony
All right, let's take over the world!