The Kirishina Corporation.
Formerly known as
Kirishina Aerospace Heavy Industries, Inc.
As its name implies, it was founded to produce and sell space planes,
for travel within the solar system,
as well as personal machines like laser-guided vehicles, or LGVs, for interplanetary travel.
Since then, it has expanded into other industries such as insurance and finance,
becoming a mega-corporation in the process.
Including all of its affiliates around the solar system,
its employees number approximately 160,000.
But at the time of Kirishina's founding, around 70 years ago,
it was merely a startup founded by two high school students.
Shinamiya Renichiro
Kiryu Takahisa
They were Kiryu Takahisa and Shinamiya Renichiro.
The rocket they built with their classmates for a science fair
marked the beginning of the corporation we know today.
And to this day, there are high school students using their youthful spark and talent
to turn their dreams into reality, as those two did.
hatenai sora
Endless skies
kinou to wa chigau massara na kimochi wa
You've got this brand new feeling, one different than yesterday's
honki no kotoba wo koete motto riaru ni
It's more real than any words can describe
"kono mama ja iya da" sou itte nakidashita
You cry to yourself, "I don't want things to go on like this"
ano hi no kimi no chikai sukoshi kurai mie wo hattatte ii
But you should at least hold yourself to the vows you made
kawaranai kako shinjita mirai subete ukeireru keredo
You may be done with your past and believing in your future,
hitorikiri ja totemo kakaekirenai
but you can't face all of it alone
hakanai sora setsunai ketsui
Ephemeral skies. Hold on to your wistful determination,
mujuun datte kamawanai
as contradictory as it may be
nakama to miru yume yo, kobaruto ni somare
I'll reach my dreams together with my friends as we dye everying in cobalt
hirumu mamonaku moyashi zukuse
Don't hold back. Set everything ablaze:
namida mo egao mo yuu'utsu saemo
our tears, our smiles, and even our sorrows
ima hiraketa sekai fumidasu inochi
Take heart as the world opens up
unmei nante kaerareru
We can change our destiny
hashiridashita kaze yo, kobaruto ni somare
These winds that are building will dye everything in cobalt
kagirinaku riaru ni
and make them more real than ever before
Faculty Room
All right, the final item on our agenda...
The other day, our very own A-TEC was featured on CHK's In the Skies of Hope.
We'll be screening the show in here right after school.
All faculty members are all expected to attend, so I hope to see you there!
Oh, man...
We don't have time for this now.
Kiryu Nagisa
All right, I guess it's time to introduce our new transfer student.
This is Kiryu Nagisa-kun.
Please note that along with being a student here,
Kiryu-kun will also be serving as A-TEC's chief.
So the rumors were true!
Seriously, the new chief?
There goes my freedom of speech.
Kiryu Nagisa
Well then, anything else you wanna say, Nagisa-kun?
I'm Kiryu Nagisa.
Starting today, I'll be working alongside you all at A-TEC.
That said, this organization will only exist for another year, at most.
So I urge you all to begin exploring new career paths as soon as possible.
Needless to say, I'll make the proper arrangements
should you wish to transfer to another department, so please let me know.
You can consult me at any time.
Kiryu Nagisa
It won't be for long, but I hope we work well together.
Work well together, my foot! What kind of a greeting is that?
Kiryu Nagisa
Is there something you'd like to say, Sensei?
I mean... Sera-kun?
I assure you it's nothing, Chief!
I mean... Kiryu-kun!
That's it. Homeroom's over!
Welcome to the Weirdos' Class!
I'm Sera Mizuki.
Nice to meet you, Kiryu Nagisa-kun.
The "Weirdos' Class", huh?
Are you sure you don't mean the Red Ink Class?
I guess Management must really have it in for us.
Of course.
Despite being given an ample budget,
this class has yet to produce any worthwhile results
and has only avoided scrutiny this long because of its prestige.
And to top it all off, that scandal two days ago.
Oh, but that was—
I had already resolved the issue by myself to begin with.
Your worries and actions were completely unwarranted.
Episode 2:
Classroom of Downsizing
Kirishina Science and Technology Academy.
Built on the concept of developing world-class employees,
it is a place where people can learn with the assistance of cutting-edge technology.
Due to the academy's high placement rate
by sending its best students to work at Kirishina,
this private school is particularly
popular among engineering students.
As if it weren't exclusive enough,
there's an even more prominent class within the academy.
It's called the Advanced Technological Educational Development Class.
Otherwise known as A-TEC.
Students attend classes until noon
and then report as full employees to specialized A-TEC facilities
where they take part in crucial projects
such as improving the cutting-edge SWNPR engine.
The SWNPR engine.
Offically named the Stellar Wind Plasma Rocket Engine.
True to its name,
this engine makes use of stellar wind by compressing and converting it into plasma
thereby achieving tremendous thrust.
At this time, only space planes have clearance for its use.
However, there is one exception.
Wherein smaller vehicles are loaded with SWNPR engines
and compete to determine the fastest of all.
They call it...
SWNPR Formula Racing.
Kirishina has long competed in these races,
known as the Formula One races of Outer Space.
In fact, their participation goes back 55 years.
Not only are A-TEC students tasked with making improvements to the SWNPR engine,
they're also responsible for its development, testing,
and promotion of the vehicles used in the races themselves.
Thanks to this,
Kirishina is always under close watch by competitors and civilians alike.
Head of Education Development
Homeroom Teacher of Kirishina Academy
Kaito Sera
A-TEC is currently led by its homeroom teacher, Sera Kaito-sensei.
Sera-sensei has taken part in junior races
and has flown his own machines since grade school.
During his studies at Kirishina Academy,
he developed what would later be called the Sera Engine
entirely on his own.
He gave a stunning presentation of his engines
in his third year as a student
when all three teams flying them took the top three spots.
It was said that his success brought about a major change in the rules.
A hero of the engineering world.
You could call him a prodigy produced by A-TEC!
Why have students handle development?
I guess you could call it a never-ending science fair?
At the time of A-TEC's creation, one of it's founders,
Shinamiya Renichiro, was also a student.
So he believed that youthful
sensibilities and imagination,
as well as untapped talent were the basis of innovation.
I'm sure he always thought this was true.
Normally, are knowledge and experience
valued in the manufacturing industry?
Of course it is!
But if we continued using only the existing technology and knowledge at our disposal,
innovative creations would be even harder to come by.
I think there's a possiblilty
that Shinamiya Renichiro hoped Kirishina would be built upon the idea
that unschooled students could define a
generation with fresh new ideas of their own.
At least, that's how I see it.
As experts in their respective fields,
the students proactively think and act on their own
as they participate in these prestigious projects.
Why did they join A-TEC?
What are their goals for the future?
A-TEC Mechanic
Sera Mizuki
3rd Year
We asked each of them personally.
What made you want to join "A-TEC"?
My parents used to work here, too.
I also a have a major goal I'm working towards.
I'm home!
Hey, welcome home.
Meet Sera Mizuki-san. She's a maintenance expert and the class president.
As her name implies,
she's Sera Kaito-sensei's younger sister.
Is your brother strict?
I wouldn't call him strict...
He's just really excitable, both at work and at home!
But at home, he's more like that...
A-TEC Test pilot
Shirasaki Iris
3rd Year
Test pilot, Shirasaki Iris-san.
Easily mastering difficult-to-manuever prototypes,
she has skills that would put professional pilots to shame.
She's A-TEC's young ace.
What made you want to join "A-TEC"?
Because Mizuki said she was coming here.
She was drawn by the idea of striving towards her goal with all her friends, right?
Right.
I've temporarily closed A-TEC for today.
There's no point in going there.
Why are you so reckless?
You may be a genius pilot or whatever,
but in my eyes you're merely suicidal.
I don't think I'm being reckless.
At this rate,
you can kiss any chance you had left to go out into the field goodbye.
You're going to have a boring, ordinary life ahead of you.
You might as well get used to it now.
Shirasaki Iris.
Are you interested in Iris?
You were watching?
No, I just got here.
What do you want?
Why don't we go home together, Nagisa-kun?
I'll show you around.
Why?
Our new chief shut down operations for the day, so I have all this free time!
That's not what I meant.
Why are you concerned about me?
Well, I am the class president.
Doesn't that mean that it's my job to worry about the lone-wolf transfer student?
You've never worked at the Head Office before, right?
Hospitals that are open in the middle of the night...
Great restaurants that are also cheap!
Don't you think that's stuff you should know about?
I've got too many other things to worry about, unfortunately.
Unlike the rest of you, who have no work.
The office is that way.
I really should show you around!
No, thanks.
Hey, did you know Iris before all this?
What are you talking about?
Well, didn't you call Iris by her full name earlier?
I thought you weren't watching.
I could still hear you though. So, tell me?
I may not look it, but I am in management.
I familiarized myself with my subordinates' names and faces before coming over.
Then what's my name?
It's Mizuki. Sera Mizuki.
Let's be friends, okay?
Nagisa-kun!
I, Kiryu Nagisa, have assumed my post as of today.
Good work.
I'm truly sorry about the trouble I caused.
My late arrival must have been extremely inconvenient for you.
You went through a lot.
Thank goodness you're safe.
Be sure to make the most of your talents at the Advanced Technological Development Department.
I intend to do everything within my power to satisfy your expectations, Director.
I'm sure you know this,
but your first task is to disband A-TEC.
I see that you're feeling quite threatened by that group of brats.
It's a negative legacy from Shinamiya that isn't worth our time.
If we used that scandal from just two days back,
wouldn't it be easy to disband—
If we did that, that Coldwood affair that we bent over backwards to cover up would come to light!
You understand that, don't you?
I don't care how you go about it.
Just do whatever you've always done.
In that case,
I wish you could've stopped them from airing that PR stunt at a time like this.
The person you succeeded, Sasayama, proposed it to the station.
It seems he caught wind of our plans and decided to stunt progress with propaganda.
So for now, any flagrant move we make will only turn the public against us.
But this can't be delayed.
I'm giving you a time limit of six months.
If you can't get it done by then...
Have I ever failed to deliver on any of your requests, Director?
That's enough. Get back to work.
Good day.
Oh, wait. One more thing...
What is it now?
That trouble in Coldwood...
I promise you that I'll prevent it from happening again.
Oh?
I ran into far too many snags during that trip.
The lack of communication with the locals... no...
The seemingly deliberate withholding of information...
I could've sworn there was something orchestrating it all.
What are you saying?
Nothing, really.
If you ask me, it was your immaturity
in resolving situations that was more than half to blame for this incident!
Do you?
To think that you couldn't even suppress people of such low caliber...
You're the disgrace of the Kiryu family.
Well, yes, I suppose I am.
Good day.
Hey, it was written all over your face,
Nii-san.
Huh? What are you guys doing here?
We're temporarily closed, right?
I didn't feel like going home, for some reason.
If you come to work without a job to do,
the labor section's gonna bust you.
Right! So why don't we all get busted together, Co-conspirator-san?
Well, staying in a group helps with the anxiety.
There's a chance we might not even have a place to come to by tomorrow.
Kiryu Nagisa was the transfer student's name, right?
He's our chief, so you probably shouldn't address him like that.
But he's a student just like us, isn't he?
Seriously... what's his deal, anyway?
His name is Kiryu, so he must be related to CEO Kiryu.
Not just any relative!
My info says he's the younger brother of CEO Kiryu Kazuhito and Director Kiryu Yuuji!
That means he's a direct heir!
No wonder he's so high up.
Yeah, but have you ever heard about there being a third son?
No.
Not like we've ever seen him on the organization chart.
That's what seems suspicious.
I mean, the HR info might as well be in Fort Knox!
Hey, hey, big news!
Seems like the transfer student is a pretty big deal!
Kiryu Nagisa joined the company at 16.
In the last two years, he's bounced around Europa, Ganymede, Callisto...
And he's moved up the corporate ladder with each transfer.
He's a super-businessman!
What's up with that?
What's so elite about this career trajectory?
Well, if he's shot up the ladder this fast, he must be elite.
I mean, he's clearly being groomed for an executive position, right?
If he is, these assignments are beyond atrocious.
What do you mean by that?
Every one of them is a satellite in the boonies.
And all these satellites are the ones with numerous problems,
or places barely functioning as cities...
They're not places you'd ship off anyone considered elite.
I know, right!?
But look, he's still been crazy successful everywhere they sent him.
And now he's become our chief at the head office!
Europa didn't have a single dealership,
Congrats on Over 120 Locations!
but thanks to him, 120 opened up within six months.
On Ganymede, he lobbied the local politicians to repeal a fuel regulation measure.
And on Callisto, he worked to open an LGV junction!
Look at that, you all came!
Mizuki?
Nii-chan would be gushing if he saw this!
Faculty Lounge
Good job, everyb—
Oh crap! That's right!
What made you want to join "A-TEC"?
Because I thought this would be the perfect environment
Combustion Tester
Yamaki Subaru
2nd year
to build the best SWNPR engine ever.
To be honest, it was either this or an LGV designer, but...
Designer
Kitahara Kojiro
3rd year
I know this'll look better on my resume.
I wanted to come here the second I heard Sera Kaito would be our teacher!
Engine Maintenance
Kaminagaya Aki
2nd year
Because no other place would give students this much freedom.
IT Engineer
Maioka Sakugo
2nd year
Maybe I'll keep repeating my grade forever.
Operator
Takanashi Kaoruko
1st year
I'm fluent in lots of languages,
so I wanted to make the most of that skill at A-TEC, my dream class!
Since math is my best subject,
Accounting, Administration
Nouen Yuna
2nd year
I wanted to put that skill to use.
Materials Engineer
Ryouke Makoto
3rd year
Well, there are lots of reasons,
but the biggest one is the salary, I guess?
I've got siblings to look after!
PR, Promotion
Hanaoka Tsubasa
2nd year
Because I wanted to stand out!
Also, this...
Someday, I'd like to become a newscaster!
I'm looking at you, CHK-san!
The students' goals and dreams are certainly diverse.
Seriously... those kids...
And here we have Sera Kaito-san in the studio with us!
Hello.
How should I put it?
There's so much more to Kirishina than I thought.
With its flexible philosophy,
it must attract a lot of interesting people, right?
Right.
If it didn't, we never would have found the potential for innovation
that's brought about by the melding of both traditional and new ideas.
Meaning?
Thanks to the SWNPR engine prototype built by one of our founders,
Shinamiya Renichiro, as a student,
the aerospace industry was revolutionized,
and because travel within the solar system became even more instantaneous for humankind,
they were able to make economic advances as well.
That ended up becoming Kirishina's foundation,
but I'm sure his goal was just to invent something new.
Something he could contribute to society.
So that must be what drove his innovation.
I see.
So I'm not speaking for just us,
but also for the students who'll be graduating from A-TEC.
I'd like us all to continue striving for innovation!
I see.
However, it's our duty to keep the spirit of Shinamiya Renichiro alive!
Um, we're almost out of time...
Of course, I'm not saying that expanding into insurance and finance is a bad thing.
Sure, without any profits, we can't make a living!
But if we forget our roots and policies as rocket-makers...
All right, we're out of time, so that's it for today.
Thank you very much, Sera-san!
Really, that was magnificent, Sera-sensei!
Thank you for your hard work!
Sera-sensei...?
That's it!
Of course that's it!
Nagisa!
Your utter disregard for seniority is rather disturbing.
Where's your formality?
Please forgive me.
However, subordinate or not,
isn't it also social etiquette to speak respectfully to your elders?
All right, then. You can call me Nagisa.
No respect for either of us.
Alright then, Kiryu Nagisa!
I won't accept your way of doing things!
Where'd this come from?
Did your speech from that show
appearence fire you up?
You got that right!
I wasn't wrong!
Whether you accept them or not,
my assignment here was a company decision.
Disgruntled?
If so, feel free to drag me down.
I don't care what underhanded methods you use.
Oh, I will.
But I'm gonna do it fair and square!
We won't let you have your way with A-TEC—you'll see!
We're going to show the top management
that we're more useful than you could ever be!
Fine. Let's see you do it.
Go ahead and convince the current management.
Before I take over as CEO, that is.
What? Huh?
Are you actually planning that far ahead?
Minami kaze ga toorisugite yuku
The southern winds blowing through
sazanami ni awasete yureru kokoro
set my heart in motion like rippling waves
mayoi nante, hitotsumonaitte omoikomasete
Make me believe that I shouldn't be worried
asu, iemasuyouni
"Tomorrow. I'll say it then,"
nandomo kurikaeshi
is what I told myself over and over
omoikaeshi aruita
as I wandered aimlessly about
hanarebanare demo ii
I don't care if we're separated,
onnaji yume dewanai aa dekinai
but our dreams are so far apart that I can't do it
demo ne honne wa ienai
I can't tell you my true feelings
mada ienaiyo
At least, not yet
tsuyogari ga yowane datte
I'm sure that you still don't know
kitto kimi wa mada wakaranai hazu
that pretending to be strong is my cry for help
aitai samishii
I want to see you, I'm lonely
kono mama tomodachi ja iyadayo
I don't want us to just be friends forever
I can understand your misgivings over a forbidden relationship between teacher and student.
But it can't be helped!
Are you out of your mind?
I think it's fine the way it is.
What's going on, Kaitocchi?
At any rate, this is unacceptable!
Episode 3:
The Woman Came
From the Accounting
Department