While it doesn't work as a 500 million yen request,
they're fine as individual requests for 20 million.
You've clearly expressed both your needs and the effects in numbers.
There's no overlap, either.
Even if I'd checked it beforehand, I couldn't have vetoed it.
Well, if you'd sent over all 30 at once, I would've stopped it there.
Just you wait, Kiryu Nagisa.
You really are a thorn in my side, Sera Kaito.
hatenai sora
Endless skies
kinou to wa chigau massara na kimochi wa
You've got this brand new feeling, one different than yesterday's
honki no kotoba wo koete motto riaru ni
It's more real than any words can describe
"kono mama ja iya da" sou itte nakidashita
You cry to yourself, "I don't want things to go on like this"
ano hi no kimi no chikai sukoshi kurai mie wo hattatte ii
But you should at least hold yourself to the vows you made
kawaranai kako shinjita mirai subete ukeireru keredo
You may be done with your past and believing in your future,
hitorikiri ja totemo kakaekirenai
but you can't face all of it alone
hakanai sora setsunai ketsui
Ephemeral skies. Hold on to your wistful determination,
mujuun datte kamawanai
as contradictory as it may be
nakama to miru yume yo, kobaruto ni somare
I'll reach my dreams together with my friends as we dye everything in cobalt
hirumu mamonaku moyashi zukuse
Don't hold back. Set everything ablaze:
namida mo egao mo yuu'utsu saemo
our tears, our smiles, and even our sorrows
ima hiraketa sekai fumidasu inochi
Take heart as the world opens up
unmei nante kaerareru
We can change our destiny
hashiridashita kaze yo, kobaruto ni somare
These winds that are building will dye everything in cobalt
kagirinaku riaru ni
and make them more real than ever before
September 5
I gave you orders to shut down A-TEC,
so why haven't they stopped their R&D work?
Actually, I was ordered to sever the ties between the Oozora Party
and Sera Kaito by whatever means necessary.
And how is giving them access to our resources any better!?
Come to think of it, did you manage to buy out Tsuda Heavy Industries yet?
It's a mere 5 billion yen deal,
and I think I gave you a week to wrap it up.
Oh, that deal?
I've already gotten Tsuda to sign a preliminary agreement.
Impossible. It should've taken you at least a month!
And yet you asked me to do it in a week anyway?
The funding process will be completed by the end of tomorrow.
The deal will be officially closed after that.
Is that right? Good work.
Now you can get on with dismantling A-TEC.
Yes, of course.
Then get out of my sight.
Episode 5:
The Shame of the
Journey Overrides
Next Day
You cry to yourself, "I don't want things to go on like this."
But you should at least hold yourself
to the vows you made.
You may be done with your past
and believing in your future,
but you can't face all of it alone
Ephemeral skies. Hold on to your wistful determination
as contradictory as it may be.
Want another?
I'll reach my dream together with my friends
as we dye everything in cobalt.
Don't hold back. Set everything ablaze: our tears, our smiles, and even—
Excuse me, Sera-sensei!
What's up?
Would you mind putting a stop to all this insanity!?
Why?
Everyone's having a good time.
That's not the issue here!
Can't you see that it's hindering Nagisa-sama's work!?
The class has been waiting for this big event all year!
Just forget about work for today.
Both Nagisa and I already told you we couldn't make it today!
We had a lot on our plate thanks to a certain someone.
So the class trip had to be pushed back until now.
And that "someone" is you!
You're missing the point here!
Let me explain.
With the designs for the new SWNPR engine and X-3 finished,
this trip is supposed to help us relax before we hit the lab!
We might be enemies, but this is still a class trip.
Nagisa-sama is supposed to be wrapping up an important deal today!
Nevermind that.
Isn't it unsafe to carry around a laptop with that much important data on it?
Not a problem. I'm using a thin client.
Everything is saved to the head-office server.
We'd only have a problem if someone else knew my password.
Didn't you know it's unsafe to carry around a laptop with that much important data on it?
Why, you little...!
Let's go!
No way! Whoa!
Cheers!
Lookin' good! Throttle up!
Hey, hurry up!
Wait up!
Coming your way, Iris!
Okay!
That's our Shirasaki-senpai!
One point for Team Makoto!
Why don't you play with us, Nagisa-kun?
Beach volleyball!
Don't you get that I'm working?
Come on. Do you really have to do it here?
I didn't know I had to follow the crowd.
Hey! What are you two doing!?
Don't you lay a finger on my sister!
I'm the victim here.
That's right!
Step away from Nagisa-sama!
Oh, what about you, Angelina-sensei? Play beach volleyball with us!
What are you talking about?
I have a job to do, which is assisting Nagisa-sama in his work.
Then why are you in a swimsuit?
Uh, no, this is... Um...
Come on, play with us!
Little brat...
Stay away from Mizuki.
Iris?
Iris, what's wrong?
Get away from her.
That woman is dangerous.
It's fine, Iris.
Angelina-sensei may be strict,
but she's a Kirishina employee, just like us!
It's not like she's secretly a secret agent or an assassin or a ninja or something!
Right, Sensei?
Well, of course I'm not!
Shirasaki Iris.
Don't talk to me like we're friends.
Why not?
Is it because you don't even know if that's your real name?
What's that supposed to mean?
You suffer from amnesia, am I right?
Your childhood is completely lost to you.
How did you know?
That's something only my brother and I know about!
Well, that's...
none of your business!
Nagisa-sama, please forgive me!
Hattori-kun, where's your tablet?
In my room at the hotel...
I see. I'm going to borrow it, then.
Right...
You're out of control.
Wow! Amazing!
Isn't this great?
Delicious!
This tuna is delicious!
Delicious.
This all-new PET bottle rocket...
can even be re-launched!
Huh? Where's Kaitocchi?
He left with Angelina-sensei a while ago.
Oh, they went off together? How suspicious.
Is it that suspicious?
Come on, it's totally shady!
Kaitocchi can't be left alone for even a second!
Come eat with the rest of us, Nagisa-kun.
No, thank you.
You'll work your life away at this rate.
Want me to make you some rice balls?
Why?
That way you can eat and work at the same time, right?
No, that's not what I meant.
Why me?
I've given Nagisa-sama everything that I can offer.
I just want to be useful to him.
And yet!
And yet, look!
Listen, don't you think you've had enough?
Shut up!
Stop interrupting, and drink!
Let's go take a bath!
All righty!
Huh? Aren't you guys going?
Well, I'm still full from dinner,
so I think I'll head over in a little while.
How about you, Iris-chan?
If Mizuki's not going, neither am I.
We'll meet you there later, then!
Yeah.
Okay, see you!
You're the ones who broke it.
Take responsibility and fix it.
It was an accident. You can't get mad at us for that.
That's right! And it's your fault for working on vacation!
Is that any way to talk to your chief?
Who are you to talk?
Some attitude, from a transfer student from the lowest rung of the school caste.
That's right! That's right!
School caste?
Yup. You heard him.
Hey, come here!
Give him...
What, what?
A mission...
I like it!
Sounds good.
Listen up, transfer student.
We'll fix that tablet for you, but we've got conditions.
Conditions?
We wanna do something,
and you've got to lend us a hand.
If you do, we'll fix your tablet.
I don't have time for negotiations.
Fine.
What do you need help with?
It's beautiful! I like it! I like it!
All units, all units, come check.
Kilo 02, check.
Kilo 03, check.
What the hell is this?
Hey, Kilo 04!
Don't take your eyes off the rear!
I'm doing this for my job...
Go!
This steam is blocking my view!
No... This steam will definitely clear up!
Actually, are you sure about this, Subaru?
Of course I am! I really wanna see it!
I-Is that right?
Don't tell me...
You're going to peek at them bathing?
There's no turning back now.
Everybody... STAY, NO, STAY's the call!
Sakugo!
Yeah, STAY!
Subaru!
STAY!
Transfer student!
He bailed.
Whatever. We're gonna stay till the steam clears.
Copy that!
I was a fool for thinking I could depend on people like them.
I need to find another way to fix it.
Whoops...
Houston, we have a problem!
Those morons fell for it.
It was a good idea to set it up at the ideal peeping spot.
That's a little too much gun powder, don't you think?
Well, it won't kill them.
Isn't that lovely?
Wow!
So people really do fall for that kind of thing!
Is your work coming along okay?
Sorry. It's not like Subaru and the guys meant any harm.
Thanks to them, if I can't access the Kirishina server by the end of today,
a 5 billion yen deal will go down the drain.
5 billion?
Uh, hey!
I thought of a way you might be able to access the server!
I looked into it, and there's a Kirishina branch office in the next town over.
How far is it from here?
I think they said it's a two-hour drive.
I've only got an hour...
Mizuki?
Even then, you guys still...
I hear you! I totally hear you!
Is that right? You get it, then?
I just wanna do the right thing for my students!
Man, I can still hear those fireworks going off.
Maybe a bath will fix everything.
Oh, I'll just use the bathroom in here.
Why?
Hey... hold up!
Hold up!
Are you insane!?
I'm trying to get there in time.
I know work is serious stuff, but...
No.
This is for Mizuki.
KIRISHINA CORPORATION
17th BRANCH
No good, huh?
Just as I thought, our computer doesn't have the clearance.
We can't access the head office server with this.
Nagisa-sama, are you in front of a computer?
Yeah, but...
What's this?
You've just been granted access to the head office server.
Can you confirm that?
Yeah! Thanks, Hattori-kun.
I'll call you back later!
Yes?
Right...
I see.
Nagisa-sama...
I'm very sorry about everything that's happened...
As long as you make sure it doesn't happen again, it's fine.
Anyway, I never knew you were skilled with computers.
No, it was Maioka-kun who took care of it all.
That guy?
I see.
Right then, I'll be awaiting your return.
All right!
You should've just done that from the start!
You worthless...
Ouch!
This is kinda nice...
No need to rush any more, all right?
I know.
You're as reckless as ever, aren't you?
But we made it.
Tell me, why did you come to Kirishina Academy?
Because Mizuki said she was going there.
Iris, I'm heading in first, okay?
Yeah.
What a coincidence!
I'm glad you were able to make it on time.
Thanks to you guys, I might not have been able to.
Hey, Nagisa-kun...
What Angelina-sensei said this afternoon...
You know, about Iris's amnesia...
Nagisa-kun?
Nagisa-kun, what's wrong?
It's nothing!
You scared me.
I thought you passed out!
You really are a busybody.
Why are you so concerned about me?
At first it was just because I wanted to get to know you better,
but then I realized you're actually a nice person.
You act mean, but that's not the real you, is it?
I am a villain.
I don't plan on befriending any of you,
and I'll do whatever it takes to achieve my goals.
You'd better watch your back, too.
But you did come on the school trip.
Thanks to your idiot brother, yes.
You wouldn't have come if you really didn't want to, right?
Did you have fun?
Of course not.
This was my first school trip,
and now I don't want to go on another one!
This was your first time?
Did you make some good memories?
More like the worst!
Really?
What are you doing here?
What? What? What?
What's wrong, Nagisa—
Nagisa...kun?
No, it's not what you think!
Mizuki...
What did you do to Mizuki?
You idiot! Stay away from me!
Really, Iris!?
What did you do to Mizuki!?
I told you the men's bath and women's bath would be switched after midnight!
Never mind! Just get out of here!
What did you do to Mizuki!?
Minami kaze ga toorisugite yuku
The southern winds blowing through
sazanami ni awasete yureru kokoro
set my heart in motion like rippling waves
mayoi nante, hitotsumonaitte omoikomasete
Make me believe that I shouldn't be worried
asu, iemasuyouni
"Tomorrow. I'll say it then,"
nandomo kurikaeshi
is what I told myself over and over
omoikaeshi aruita
as I wandered aimlessly about
hanarebanare demo ii
I don't care if we're separated,
onnaji yume dewarai atte itai
I just want to laugh with you, sharing the same dream
demo ne honne wa ienai
I can't tell you my true feelings
mada ienaiyo
At least, not yet
tsuyogari ga yowane datte
I'm sure that you still don't know
kitto kimi wa mada wakaranai hazu
that pretending to be strong is my cry for help
aitai samishii
I want to see you, I'm lonely
kono mama tomodachi ja iyadayo
I don't want us to just be friends forever
Why did I drink so much?
Mizuki-chan! Give us a hand, too!
What's the problem?
You've got two others with you!
Don't drink too much, okay?
Oh, no, you're staying with us till morning!
Sorry. Maybe that was power harassment?
Episode 6:
Family of Shame