Cut it by 70 percent?
You mean A-TEC's budget?
That's right. I've made adjustments to all relevant departments.
You should be grateful.
I'm sure Accounting was thrilled.
Now it doesn't matter how much support A-TEC has,
as they'll just self-destruct once their budget runs dry.
You didn't have to take those measures, Director.
If you'd just left it to me...
You just need to do exactly what I tell you to!
You're always ignoring our orders,
taking matters into your own hands!
Forgive me for saying so, Nii-san,
but I've achieved major success in every region I've been assigned to.
So this time as well—
The results aren't the problem!
Your refusal to obey me is the problem!
Listen here...
Do as you're told, and we might just get along.
That's all.
Dismissed!
One more thing...
You are not to call me "Nii-san."
It's me.
I've got more work for you to do.
hatenai sora
Endless skies
kinou to wa chigau massara na kimochi wa
You've got this brand new feeling, one different than yesterday's
honki no kotoba wo koete motto riaru ni
It's more real than any words can describe
"kono mama ja iya da" sou itte nakidashita
You cry to yourself, "I don't want things to go on like this"
ano hi no kimi no chikai sukoshi kurai mie wo hattatte ii
But you should at least hold yourself to the vows you made
kawaranai kako shinjita mirai subete ukeireru keredo
You may be done with your past and believing in your future,
hitorikiri ja totemo kakaekirenai
but you can't face all of it alone
hakanai sora setsunai ketsui
Ephemeral skies. Hold on to your wistful determination,
mujuun datte kamawanai
as contradictory as it may be
nakama to miru yume yo, kobaruto ni somare
I'll reach my dreams together with my friends as we dye everying in cobalt
hirumu mamonaku moyashi zukuse
Don't hold back. Set everything ablaze:
namida mo egao mo yuu'utsu saemo
our tears, our smiles, and even our sorrows
ima hiraketa sekai fumidasu inochi
Take heart as the world opens up
unmei nante kaerareru
We can change our destiny
hashiridashita kaze yo, kobaruto ni somare
These winds that are building will dye everything in cobalt
kagirinaku riaru ni
and make them more real than ever before
Can't get the output to stabilize, huh?
Looks like it needs more repairs than we thought.
Do you think we'll have to replace most of the parts?
Good work, everyone!
How's it looking?
We just found out there's no hope in repairing it as is.
In any case, we've got to determine what needs replacing by the end of the day.
The end of the day?
Let's do our best, guys!
We'll get this awesome engine running again,
and show that bastard chief what we're made of!
Yeah!
A teacher calling his student a bastard...
B-But Sensei...
Our current budget won't be enough to repair...
Don't worry, just leave it to me!
You guys don't have to worry about a thing!
Tasty.
a.m.
Episode 3:
The Woman Came
From the Accounting
Department
So, what did you want?
Asking for a meeting this early in the morning...
You're the only one who's actually free at this time of day!
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
Why don't you take a look at this!
Auxiliary booster
SWNPR KSX-4
repair parts order
New radar sensor avionics order
Cockpit block repair parts order
X-2 repair plan
New radar sensor
avionics order
New booster
development quote
New radar sensor
avionics order
New booster
development quote
SWNPR
repair parts
New radar sensor
avionics order
New booster
development quote
SWNPR
repair parts
Cockpit block repair
parts order
X-2 repair plan
So anyway...
What do you expect me to do with just a parts list and its cost estimate?
We're going to need 750 million to repair the X-2's SWNPR engine.
I'm requesting additional funds!
Are you insane?
I'm dead serious!
At this rate, you won't even last three months...
What do you mean?
What the hell are you doing!?
Did you think a request like this would actually get approved?
What, circulars aren't good enough for you?
What's a circular?
Y-You should already know that...
Genius engineer, my foot!
You're just a rocket nerd with bad spending habits.
What did you say!?
Chief Sasayama never had a problem with this sort of thing!
Let me tell you why it worked for you till now.
You were getting biased treatment...
And not in a good way.
X-2 repair plan
I mean, what is this?
This only outlines costs.
Show me some results!
Tell me what your goals are!
Tell me what's so important about this project,
and how your work will impact the company.
Why is investing in you the right choice?
It'll be a circular once you've figured that all out!
If you don't understand what I'm saying, you have no right to do business.
Go back to the lab and sulk over your lack of funding some more.
Sensei, are you all right?
Sensei?
C-Come back here!
We're not done yet!
We'd better head to school or we'll both be late... Sera-sensei.
Good morning!
We're gonna be late.
Okay...
I wanted to take a shower,
but then we'd be late for class.
Going like this is fine, too.
As a girl, you should really care more about this stuff.
You guys really are the workaholics of the team...
What's wrong?
There's someone in the office.
Who's that?
No clue...
Uh, excuse me, but who are you?
Only A-TEC members are allowed in here, you know
What are you planning to do with the papers in this box?
Answer me!
How are you planning to dispose of these papers?
Well, we just leave it around until the cleaning lady collects it.
And what happens after she collects them?
Incineration? Shredding?
Are you selling them to the recyclers?
We leave that up to the cleaning lady. Is that a problem?
In other words, you don't take the time to sort them before they're taken?
Rather than using the reverse side of sheets with glaring misprints
or papers that aren't in the least bit confidential, you just waste these?
You're even throwing rocket sketches and meeting minutes in here!
These papers contain company secrets!
You're essentially leaking them to outsiders!
Your cost-consciousness and sense of confidentiality are far too lax!
You lack the discipline you should already have as working adults!
The situation here is far worse than I expected.
To think that we'd been entrusting
Kirishina's precious budget to a bunch of brats... what a joke!
Brats?
And just who exactly are you, old lady?
Stooping to cheap shots bordering on sexual harassment to bait me
is typical brat behavior!
But you totally just fell for it...
Oh, you're that type of person!
Abusing your status as a veteran and insulting others for no reason...
the classic femme fata—
Prostrate yourself and apologize.
I'm still in my twenties.
Sexual harassment is a no-no, but abuse of power is fine?
Where's the intruder!?
Help me, Kaitocchi!
What're you doing to my student!?
You're Sera Kaito?
Leader and homeroom teacher of A-TEC, who,
despite being a cute 23-year-old, is annoying to the point
of having no girlfriend?
Well, that last thing...
Wait, how do you know my age!?
Not to mention
Nagisa's enemy, who incurred a loss of 16 billion in just one day?
Seriously, who are you?
I'm Angelina from Budget Management in Accounting.
Kirishina Corporation
Accounting Department, Budget Management
As of today,
I'll be working here at the Advanced
Technological Development Department.
What the...?
Moreover...
I'll also be serving as A-TEC's vice-homeroom teacher.
I look forward to working with you!
Angelina
You are Japanese, right?
No, I'm Angelina.
Then what's your family name?
I'm simply Angelina.
Nothing more and nothing less.
Nah... I'll bet anything she's got a real name.
This is A-TEC's hangar.
But I'm sure you've already read about it in the files.
Would it be all right if I took some photos?
They won't leave the office, of course.
Well then, go ahead.
By the way, there's something I'd like to ask you, Angelina-sensei.
What is it?
By any chance, are you involved with Kiryu Nagisa?
I can understand your misgivings over a forbidden relationship between teacher and student.
However, at this time,
we've done nothing to feel guilty about.
Although that only holds true "at this time..."
No, that's not what I was getting at.
Did Kiryu Nagisa summon you here?
Yes.
For now, I work for the Advanced
Technological Development Department
operating under the chief's supervision, managing costs here at A-TEC.
So that's why you were transferred from Accounting.
Listen, can you help us out a bit?
You should try helping yourselves first.
Hear me out, Angelina-sensei.
We're working with cutting-edge technology here.
Sure, developing SWNPR engines for racing vehicles
isn't going to make the company any money right now.
It'll take five years for this technology to hit the market.
No, maybe even ten years!
Still!
That's precisely why!
Siding with us is an investment in this company's future!
Yes, if this company is still racing ten years from now.
What?
Jeez, you're so annoying!
My hands are tied here!
But...
Listen to me! This is for your own good.
A-TEC will be disbanded if you keep bleeding money like this,
and you'll only last three months at most.
That's how big a thorn in
management's side you people are!
What's that?
If that happens, calling out
"We'll pay you back double!",
"Let's win it with one blast!",
or "Pull back from the brink of disaster!" won't work!
Hey, calm down...
It'd be in your best interest to
cooperate with my budget plans.
Fine!
Let's hear your proposal.
But whatever you do, just please don't downsize my students.
I'm a teacher first, and an employee second.
It's my job to protect them no matter what.
Please!
Do you honestly think you've been protecting them this whole time?
I saw students in the engine room this morning, and they all looked exhausted.
A lot of them, at that.
Well, we want to repair our machine as quickly as possible...
Long hours with no days off,
and working overtime late into the night...
From what I saw, that seems to be the norm here.
How do you feel about forcing minors to work such relentless schedules?
And you didn't even realize till now.
Plus, you can't even manage costs or work habits.
You tyrant boss!
Tyrant boss?
Since you asked nicely,
I'll abstain from firing your students.
However, I can't be held accountable if they choose to resign or quit school on their own.
Me? A tyrant?
The Next Day
Huh?
What's the problem?
I can't get in.
What's this?
Was there a system shutdown memo posted?
Not that I know of.
Bad news!
The hell is this?
I mean... there's no telling what's what.
What's going on, Kaitocchi!?
That should be obvious.
All A-TEC facilities have been transferred to the Manufacturing Department,
and the Advanced Technological Development Department now has a consumer LGV production line!
Hold up a second!
Th-This whole factory, in just one day?
Yes. After receiving Sera-sensei's permission,
we pulled an all nighter to get it fully operational.
If I'm a tyrant, what does this make you!?
You didn't really give your permission, did you, Nii-san?
Of course I did—
Fine!
Let's hear your proposal.
Nii-san?
Did you tell her it was okay to get rid of our space?
Where are we gonna work now?
Everybody, calm down.
Nii-san, can you explain?
You mentioned a budget cut,
but you never said anything about taking away our factory!
No need to worry.
I've secured an alternate work space for you.
R-Really?
Yes.
It's somewhat smaller than you're used to,
but it's certainly the most suitable place for A-TEC.
Isn't this the Kirishina Memorial Building?
It was closed down two years ago,
and it's no longer needed as a memorial building.
The Kirishina Corporation was able to preserve the garage
that its founders, Kiryu Takahisa and Shinamiya Renichiro, built their very first rockets in.
Important Aerospace Heritage
X-58 A.K.A: Shinamiya Rocket
will be remembered as an important
part of aerospace history
Kirishina Corporation Aerospace Association
Now that the building is no longer in use, you've been given full access to the facility.
Hey, don't tell me...
That's right!
This is where A-TEC was born!
A rather fitting place to hold your base of operations, don't you think?
This is just some sick joke, right?
The only joke I'm aware of is your lax attitude towards the status quo!
The factory that you had been playing around in until now...
Do you realize how much it costs just to keep it running year-round?
Hundreds of millions just for the heat and electricity, and if we included other expenses,
you wouldn't make enough to pay us back,
even if you all worked for the rest of your lives!
That's already a heavy burden...
According to my calculations, A-TEC can still operate here at one-twentieth the cost.
Sure it can, but...
We won't be able to get anything done in here without any proper equipme—
Money isn't everything! Use your creativity!
But that'll only get us so far!
This is non-negotiable.
You can either accept this fate and hope for A-TEC's survival,
or you can leave while you still can.
I'll leave that choice up to you.
Old man, another round!
All right, give me a sec.
Haven't you had a bit too much to drink?
How can I not drink after what happened, Chief?
I'm not your chief anymore, you know.
That's right.
Damn!
Chief, you bastard!
Montsuu
Grilled Chicken Shop
Birin Beer
I see, so they kicked you out of the factory.
Half of the team left, too.
Why are you two leaving?
We've all worked together for two whole years!
What else is there to do?
They already said a promotion isn't likely.
And I've got a job offer somewhere else.
Even if I stayed, what would I be able to do here?
Subaru-kun?
Kaitocchi, I wish you had put up more of a fight.
We're just getting started!
It's not over yet!
Mizuki...
It's all right.
Hey, Sasayama-san,
all those sacrifices we had to make, all the hours we put in...
What was all that for?
The company had a sudden change in policy,
and now they don't want anything to do with us.
They called us useless, and even took away our home...
But you've still got a chance to prove yourselves.
You were told to rely on creativity instead of money, right?
They're not wrong in that regard.
Have you been protecting me all this time, Sasayama-san?
Were you giving me biased treatment?
For better or for worse, you're special.
Whereas some might see you at the center of corporate strategy,
others won't want anything to do with you.
That's the kind of talent you possess.
I just want to keep pursuing my dreams.
And that's exactly why he needs you.
Hey, Nagisa-sama?
How about we have a toast to celebrate our reunion?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm still a minor.
You're always saying,
"Don't get trapped in existing rules,"
yet you're conservative about the weirdest things...
Still, you're being quite lenient with them, Nagisa-sama.
Nii-san just told me the same thing.
If you just leave them to do whatever,
they'll definitely burn through their budget and self-destruct.
You accounting pros sure are harsh.
That's just it.
The fact that you need me here to begin with
means that you want me to keep things steady.
In other words, it's life-support.
I've got to keep it running, if only for a short time.
I've got my own battle to fight, after all.
Nagisa-sama, about your request concerning Director Kiryu's movements...
Did you find out anything?
Regarding A-TEC's budget cuts,
nobody knows anything about it;
not finance, accounting, or even the administration
It must be top-secret then,
and only top management has been notified.
If even the department chiefs are in the dark about this,
then it's not top secret...
It might not have existed in the first place.
Or...
I wonder where all that money is going to?
I'll continue to keep an eye on Director Kiryu.
You'll be first to hear about anything.
I'm counting on you,
Hattori-kun...
Please don't call me by that name...
Nagisa-sama...
I'm gonna jump in the shower now, so let yourself out.
But I thought we were about to share a night of passion
after not being able to see each other for so long!
I only agreed to let you use my shower, and nothing else.
Seriously! You have the weirdest boundaries!
Minami kaze ga toorisugite yuku
The southern winds blowing through
sazanami ni awasete yureru kokoro
set my heart in motion like rippling waves
mayoi nante, hitotsumonaitte omoikomasete
Make me believe that I shouldn't be worried
asu, iemasuyouni
"Tomorrow. I'll say it then,"
nandomo kurikaeshi
is what I told myself over and over
omoikaeshi aruita
as I wandered aimlessly about
hanarebanare demo ii
I don't care if we're separated,
onnaji yume dewanai aa dekinai
but our dreams are so far apart that I can't do it
demo ne honne wa ienai
I can't tell you my true feelings
mada ienaiyo
At least, not yet
tsuyogari ga yowane datte
I'm sure that you still don't know
kitto kimi wa mada wakaranai hazu
that pretending to be strong is my cry for help
aitai samishii
I want to see you, I'm lonely
kono mama tomodachi ja iyadayo
I don't want us to just be friends forever
All right, which is going to survive?
A-TEC,
or me?
Or else...
Hold it!
There's a big difference between "not having a girlfriend"
and "never having a girlfriend, ever!"
Either way, just ask her! As a friend, of course...
Are you consoling me?
I see... you're consoling me!
You shouldn't ask me...
Episode 4
Duel! Union Battle
You're as annoying as ever!