hatenai sora
Endless skies
kinou to wa chigau massara na kimochi wa
You've got this brand new feeling, one different than yesterday's
honki no kotoba wo koete motto riaru ni
It's more real than any words can describe
"kono mama ja iya da" sou itte nakidashita
You cry to yourself, "I don't want things to go on like this"
ano hi no kimi no chikai sukoshi kurai mie wo hattatte ii
But you should at least hold yourself to the vows you made
kawaranai kako shinjita mirai subete ukeireru keredo
You may be done with your past and believing in your future,
hitorikiri ja totemo kakaekirenai
but you can't face all of it alone
hakanai sora setsunai ketsui
Ephemeral skies. Hold on to your wistful determination,
mujuun datte kamawanai
as contradictory as it may be
nakama to miru yume yo, kobaruto ni somare
I'll reach my dreams together with my friends as we dye everything in cobalt
hirumu mamonaku moyashi zukuse
Don't hold back. Set everything ablaze:
namida mo egao mo yuu'utsu saemo
our tears, our smiles, and even our sorrows
ima hiraketa sekai fumidasu inochi
Take heart as the world opens up
unmei nante kaerareru
We can change our destiny
hashiridashita kaze yo, kobaruto ni somare
These winds that are building will dye everything in cobalt
kagirinaku riaru ni
and make them more real than ever before
July 25
Summer vacation
It's still just us five...
What are we gonna do, Sensei?
No people, products, or money... we're completely hopeless.
At this rate, we'll just end up sitting around and doing nothing...
H-Hey!
What if we all got part-time jobs to fund our work here?
All right.
I'll start working as an
unlicensed cabbie or bike messe—
It was just a joke!
Besides, it's against both school and
company policy to have a job on the side.
And we'd never be able to make enough
money to fund ourselves anyway, Iris-senpai.
We'd need about 500 million just to get us up and running again.
We really do burn through a lot of money,
when you think about it...
Episode 4:
Duel! Union Battle
Yo!
Lookin' a bit under the weather today.
That's the least of my problems.
You know what I'm dealing with.
Now, now...
Here's a little present to help you lighten up, Kaito-sensei.
This'll help you relieve some stress!
Go ask some girl to go with you...
How about that new assistant homeroom teacher!?
What was her name again?
Angelina.
What's her real name?
That's classified, apparently.
Well...
Either way, just ask her! As a friend, of course.
Is this some kind of movie? Or even a concert—
This is just a ticket to some politician's speech!
Please!
There haven't been enough RSVPs, so the union's forcing us to go,
but I've got a date with my girlfriend that day...
So why don't you just take her to the lecture?
She'd be gone before we even got through the doors!
Ah, what a nice double standard—
That's it...
The union!
What about it?
Labor Union
"An organization comprised of workers
who band together to negotiate with management
regarding wages, work hours, etc."
••  •  •
••  ••
•    •••
•          • ••
••  •  ••  •   ••  ••
•    ••  •
•  • •  •
•           •••
••  •• •   •  •
••  ••
•   •  ••
• ••  •
•••
Kirishina Corporation
Union Meeting Hall
This is how it is.
We, the members of A-TEC, have been forced into an environment that we can't work in,
stripped of our budget and tasks,
and are now suffering severe mental anguish.
This is corporate tyranny!
Kirishina
Corporation Chairman,
Labor Union
Secretary General,
All-Kirishina Federation
of Labor Unions Board Member,
Rocket
Association,
Shigeru Yamamoto
I see.
If this is true, then it
certainly is cause for concern.
It's completely true!
Completely
against
Downsizing!
Our newly-appointed chief, Kiryu Nagisa,
is working with accounting to force unrealistic budget cuts on us,
against
Completely
Downsizing!
against
Completely
Downsizing!
against
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000 yen increase!
Bonus: 5.8 months or bust!
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000 yen increase!
Bonus: 5.8 months or bust!
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000
and forcing out anyone who doesn't agree with him by harassing them with his power!
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000 yen increase!
Bonus: 5.8 months or bust!
This is "Observe Office Rules Month"
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000 yen increase!
Bonus: 5.8 months or bust!
This is "Observe Office Rules Month"
Wages: Shoot for a 4,000 yen increase!
Bonus: 5.8 months or bust!
This is "Observe Office Rules Month"
Create an environment that's easy to work in!
Bonus: 5.8 months or bust!
This is "Observe Office Rules Month"
Create an environment that's easy to work in!
Kiryu Nagisa...
The third son of the founding family, the Kiryus.
He's an elite businessman who made it high up on the corporate ladder despite his young age.
But in reality, he's just a person trying to get rid of us
to weaken the company's foundations so that he can get ahead...
He's like a termite!
Are you going to just sit around while he does whatever he wants?
Very well.
The Kirishina Corporation's union will now
support A-TEC in any way that it can manage.
Let's work together to protect the rights of our workers!
Thank you very much, Committee Chairman!
Likewise!
Enthusiastic rocket maker, Sera Kaito,
we welcome your participation in our union activities.
Right! I look forward to working with you!
By the way, I've heard it's normal at A-TEC
for underage employees to work unpaid overtime...
I don't know anything about that...
The Next Day
A-TEC is a prestigious
development department established
by our founder, Shinamiya Renichiro,
and to this day, we carry
the future of the company on our shoulders
Please help us by signing this petition
against the dismantling of A-TEC!
by striving for innovation with cutting-edge technology in a growing market...
We ask for your understanding and cooperation
so that we can save our workplace!
For Kirishina, we're an indispensable team.
However, the company is eager to cut us off, an investment for the future
What are we doing this for, anyway?
just so that they can save money.
D-Don't ask me...
I ask you, can we allow such tyranny?
All right, everybody,
let's look more towards reality!
Good morning!
Please sign our petition!
What kind of petition?
A request to recall a tyrannical boss's orders, maybe?
Just kidding!
But we can't just let A-TEC get shut down.
So...
Stop right where you are.
Kiryu Nagisa...
I'm not letting you have your way anymore!
I see, so now you're in bed with the union.
It's my legitimate right as a worker.
You got a problem with that?
Don't regret it.
The union isn't as clean and
selfless as they'd like you to think.
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Completely
Against
Dismantling
A-TEC!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Don't Let
Them
Downsize Us
By Force!
Shall I kill them?
No, let them do as they please.
This sort of stunt won't accomplish anything.
August 5
Kirishina City
Kirishina City Hall
Now, without further ado...
A man who has worked hard to reduce rocket-related taxes
and is a devoted advocate for rocket-makers.
Without him, there would no future for the industry...
Murakami Sadayuki-sensei!
Oozora Party
In-house Assemblyman,
Rocket
Association,
Murakami Sadayuki
Stop it, Nii-san.
Stop moving!
O-Okay.
Sera-sensei, you're up after this,
so please be ready.
R-Right!
Kaito-sensei, why are you making a speech for some random politician?
Yeah, now that you mention it...
What does this have to do with union activities?
Well, you know, it's because...
Why am I doing this?
Allow me to answer that question!
Oh, Committee Chairman.
In order to truly make a difference,
you have to go beyond just challenging the company.
This is true for everyone, and not just those involved in the rocket industry.
To live prosperously, safely, and happily,
we must create proactive communities
and eventually, a proactive nation!
That's why we take part in politics!
By the way,
in this voting district,
with our union's support,
we can get anyone elected,
no matter how unknown they are!
Scary! This union is scary!
How would you like to proclaim your candidacy for the upcoming general election?
If you ran, you'd be sure to win by a landslide!
Hey, I'm just a tech guy!
I'm not a politician, okay?
Oozora Party
Oozora's Dream - Giving Towards the Future
Actually, an important guest will be sharing a few words with us today...
Oozora Party
Oozora's Dream - Giving Towards the Future
You may have seen him on TV just a few days ago.
The leader of A-TEC at the Kirishina Corporation,
also known as the Hot-Blooded Rocket Teacher, Sera Kaito-san is here with us today!
Welcome, Kaito-sensei!
In regards to the upcoming election,
it's quite possible that the Oozara party could come into power again.
If that happens, it would be the perfect time for our union to go on the offensive.
So you're just using Nii-san's name to gain recognition?
In return, Sera-sensei now has the opportunity
Thank you for introducing me. I'm Sera Kaito.
to make your desperate situation public,
right here in this venue.
This will hit the company right where it hurts.
Let's give Sera Kaito-sensei a big round of applause!
"The union isn't as clean and selfless as they'd like you to think."
What's the meaning of this?
I thought I told you to make quick work of A-TEC!
Why did you let this happen?
This level of resistance was to be expected.
It's no problem for us.
The union has never called for a strike since the company was founded.
Plus, it's not really a union.
The "workers advocate" shtick is attractive,
but they'd sooner find new jobs than fight manag—
This is what I meant when I said you were naïve!
Is A-TEC joining the union really that big a deal?
The union isn't the issue!
But joining with the Oozora Party...
Anyway, find a way to get A-TEC out of the union!
I don't care how you do it!
You don't care how?
That's right! Just get it done by the end of the month.
Nagisa-sama, what did you discuss with Director Kiryu?
Hattori-kun, it's the election.
What?
My brother has something planned for the next general election.
That, or there's something else troubling him.
Director Kiryu?
I want to know what he's planning. Do some digging.
Right.
Also, please stop calling me that. I mean it.
August 20
The First Collective Bargaining
Thank you for taking the time to meet with us today, Chief Kiryu.
It's no problem, considering it's the union that asked for a meeting.
I appreciate that.
Then let's get to business.
Please take a look at those materials.
We've come to discuss the situation at A-TEC,
as requested by leader Sera.
Oh, before we go into that.
Could you wait a moment?
You. Hand it to him.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
Open it and see.
Letter of Appointment
"Sera Kaito-dono, you have been promoted to Assistant Chief
of the Advanced Technological
Development Department."
Congratulations on your promotion, Assistant Chief Sera.
As of the first of next month,
you'll be an executive.
So you still had that card to play!?
What? What does this mean?
Assistant Chief Sera, I am truly sorry...
This makes it impossible for us
to collaborate with you.
Why not?
Because you've become an executive!
Huh?
The union is solely for laborers.
Since you are now part of management,
that makes us enemies!
That's right, you corporate dog!
What? Hold up... Chairman!
Please come back! Come on... What's going on here?
Nagisa-sama...
Oh, and we'll be sure to send you a gift to celebrate your promotion.
Once again,
congratulations on your promotion.
This makes you the Advanced Technological
Development Department's No. 2.
Please help us by signing this petition
against the dismantling of A-TEC!
Please!
You guys really are hard workers...
Angelina-sensei...
I'm impressed by your perseverance.
But it's totally pointless now.
What do you mean by that?
Nagisa-sama just killed A-TEC from the inside.
It's over for you people.
Please help us by signing this petition
against the dismantling of A-TEC!
Listen to what I'm staying, you little brat!
But Nii-san would never back down just like that.
I wouldn't be so sure of that.
Even his soul must be broken this time around.
Then do you want to bet?
On whether or not my brother
would say "I give up" to your face?
Blind faith...
I don't have time for this...
Kojiro?
Sorry, you guys...
After you went all-out like that...
It's not your fault, Sensei!
That's right. It was the union that decided to cut you off.
But seriously, the company must be off its rocker.
Making a rocket nerd with no
management skills an executive!
Are you consoling me?
Yeah, you're really trying to console me.
So what are we going to do, Nii-san?
We could at least keep our protest going, right?
No, that's gonna be difficult.
We got support from the union,
but they only helped us because of Sensei.
So, should we just give up?
We could stop all the protests, and spend the rest of our time
doing nothing before we're disbanded.
I...
Until now, I've only been focused on research and development.
The classroom, labs, and the factory, were the center of my world.
As your teacher and boss, I've been pretty immature.
You've had to go through a lot because of that...
But... still...
I've never once given up on research
or development because it couldn't be done!
That's why we never stopped working at A-TEC,
and I've got my recognition as an engineer to prove it.
That's why giving up will never be an option for me, ever!
It's still not too late.
I want to become a great teacher, and a great boss for you guys!
That's why, if you're okay with it,
I'd like you guys to keep supporting me!
Man, so annoying as usual!
That was a pretty motivational speech,
but you didn't say anything about fighting back.
Leaning on the union over financial matters...
That was a bad idea to begin with.
Try a little harder, Kaitocchi!
You guys... I thought you were all done with us.
Hey, I just pretended to quit.
I actually went and convinced everyone to come back!
Huh?
Getting a little cheeky, are we?
I remember you were the first to walk out.
I really did plan on quitting.
Kojiro...
But everyone who stayed looked so hopeless, it was getting hard to watch.
Especially you...
Well, it was hard figuring things out by ourselves...
Gimme a break.
Makoto! Thank you!
You're every bit as annoying as your brother!
Right! Thanks!
Yuna, Tsubasa, Subaru-kun... thanks to you, too!
It's not like they were the only ones who stayed, you know.
This is kinda annoying.
Forget about it, you two.
Aki! Kaoruko-chan! Sakugo-kun!
Over here, over here!
Well, do we have a choice?
You too, Iris. Hurry!
All right, Class President?
All right! It's been a while,
but let's have a class meeting!
Right!
Oh, you're not starting one now.
The union restricts minors from
working overtime, so go home.
What?
Man, way to kill the mood.
We were just getting all fired up!
But I'm an executive now.
Corporate dog!
2 Weeks Later
A-TEC?
Well, I haven't gone out of my way to check on them lately...
I see.
Doesn't look like anything's really changed...
What? What's going on here?
All systems are working.
Yay! We did it!
Okay, now we've got all the parts we need!
All right! All right!
Yay!
It's too soon to celebrate!
We've got the new SWNPR engine,
the designs for the X-3, and...
Why not just celebrate today, Nii-san? Er, Sensei!
This isn't good at all!
Hey, Angelina-sensei. Welcome to our garage.
What in the world is going on here?
We're just putting in another day's work, that's all.
Where'd all this equipment come from, and how did you put it all together?
We asked our suppliers for them, of course.
Oh, and needless to say, I didn't force anyone to pull an all-nighter.
This is fraudulent accounting!
You've been amassing secret funds, haven't you?
Wrong! We used fair methods and got them through circulars!
Well, it wasn't as fair as you make it sound.
Just shut up for a second!
With Sera-sensei's promotion to Assistant Chief,
he was given both responsibilities and power.
He now has the authority to make decisions.
And if it's a single item under 20 million yen, an assistant chief
is allowed to withdraw that amount from the company without the chief's approval.
We've got an accounting pro on our side, too.
B-But there's no way you did all this with only 20 million yen!
Right. We issued 30 circulars for 20 million yen, each.
In all, we secured funds of 599,700,000 yen.
That's enough to keep us going for now.
Hold on a second!
That's a clear violation of the rules!
We can only get that much per item,
but we don't have any other limits.
The bylaws don't say anything about how much the item has to cost!
You were right. Money isn't everything, so we used our creativity instead.
We're not going to give up, ever!
So please continue to look after us, Sensei.
Angelina-sensei!
I admit we bent the rules a little bit,
but even you guys must...
Remember this.
Whether or not I let this slide, A-TEC is doomed.
That might be the case,
but we can't know unless we try!
But I know.
How many years do you think I've been working for this company?
Come to think of it, when did you start working here?
Asking a woman of marriageable
age how old she is!?
With a deviant mind like that, it's no wonder why you've been single for 23 years!
Wait a second!
There's a big difference between "not having a girlfriend" and "never having a girlfriend, ever!"
Anyway!
Don't think that you've won just yet, Sera Kaito!
Sure! The real battle is about to begin!
Hattori Hanako!
Yes, I'm looking forward to...
Wait... Why!? How did you find out my real name!?
Don't underestimate A-TEC's
information network!
Hanako-chan!
A little bird in HR clued me in, see?
You little brat!
Hey, it's a great name,
you know? Hattori Hanako!
To me, it doesn't matter whether you're Hattori or Hanako...
What do you want?
What happened to your face?
What difference does it make?
So what do you want with me?
Those 30 circulars you posted.
Accounting finished processing them,
and sent the originals to me.
Don't tell me you're gonna stop us now?
We've already used up all the money...
If you submitted it like the way you did before,
I would've put a stop to it, but...
While it doesn't work as a 500 million yen request,
they're fine as individual requests for 20 million.
You've clearly expressed both your needs and the effects in numbers.
There's no overlap, either.
Even if I'd checked it beforehand,
I couldn't have vetoed it.
Well, if you'd sent over all 30 at once,
I would've stopped it there.
Just you wait, Kiryu Nagisa.
You really are a thorn in my side, Sera Kaito.
Would you mind putting a stop to all this insanity!?
Then why are you in a swimsuit?
One point for Team Makoto!
Let's go take a bath!
Why did I drink so much?
Episode 5:
The Shame of the
Journey Overrides
You're out of control.